https://www.tesall.com/privacy.php

TESall-All TESOL-ESL EFL TESOL Teaching Jobs and Teacher Resources for Teaching English Abroad
Welcome to
TESall
All TESOL
HomeTESOL TeachersPOST Your Resume InfoPOST Your Tutoring ServiceTESOL Teaching JobsTESOL Training CoursesTESOL RecruitersTESOL Teaching ScamsTESOL Teacher ForumTESOL Teaching BlogTESOL Lesson PlansTESOL Teacher ResourcesTESOL Information - Q&ATESOL Teaching GuideTESOL ClassifiedsTESOL SchoolsPOST Your Teaching JobsPOST Your Recruiter ServicesPOST Your School InfoPOST Your Training CourseTESOL Teacher ResumesTESOL Teaching BlogTESOL Lesson PlansTESOL Teaching ResourcesTESOL Information - Q&ATESOL LinksTESOL ClassifiedsTESOL StudentsTESOL SchoolsTESOL TutorsTESOL Learning ResourcesTESOL ClassifiedsTESOL Teaching BlogTESOL Information - Q&ATESOL ArticlesTESOL LinksTESOL ResourcesTESOL ResourcesTESOL Teaching BlogTESOL Lesson PlansTESOL Jobs FeedTESOL Teaching ScamsTESOL ArticlesTESOL Information - Q&ATESOL Teaching GuideTESOL ClassifiedsTESOL Jobs FeedsTESOL Top Jobs FeedTESOL Jobs Feed AsiaTESOL Jobs Feed South KoreaTESOL Jobs Feed ChinaTESOL Jobs Feed TaiwanTESOL Jobs Feed JapanTESOL Jobs Feed Southeast AsiaTESOL Jobs Feed ThailandTESOL Jobs Feed Middle EastTESOL Jobs Feed EuropeTESOL Jobs Feed Latin AmericaTESOL Jobs Feed Central AmericaTESOL Jobs Feed South AmericaTESOL Jobs Feed North AmericaTESOL Jobs Feed AfricaTESOL Jobs Feed OceaniaTESOL Jobs Feed Online
Post Your Teaching Job Today - 10 sites for the price of one!
TESall.com Privacy Policy
Home
ESL EFL TESOL
Teach English Abroad with TESall (All TESOL), an English Language Teaching (ELT) job search portal for ESL EFL TESOL teaching jobs abroad. The TESall (All TESOL) jobs board contains the best TESOL teaching jobs from around the world updated daily.
TESOL teacher training courses are available throughout the world to get you started on your TESOL teaching adventure! You can also find information on ESL EFL TESOL teachers, resumes, teacher discussions, articles, resources and more! The result is a one-stop TESOL website that gives you access to 1000s of English teaching jobs and resources.
Where do you want to teach today?
This privacy policy sets out how TESall.com uses and protects any information that you give TESall.com when you use this website.
TESall.com is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.
TESall.com may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from January 1, 2017.
What we collect for Registered Users (if any)
We may collect the following information:
name
contact information including email address
other relevant information (user type, avatar, postings made)
What we do with the information we gather
We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:
Internal record keeping.
We may use the information to improve our services.
From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for site research and improvement purposes. We may use the information to customise the website according to your interests.
Security
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. We currently use GeoTrust Security Monitoring Services to scan and detect any security issues. Please note that Registered Users will have their contact information displayed in the Account section: Name, Email, Avatar, General Information/Bio provided by Users, Posts by Users.
Under no circumstances would TESall.com ever contact you for personal financial information.
How we use cookies
We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about webpage traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.
Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.
You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.
Links to other websites
Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
Controlling your information
We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.
You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to admin@tesall.com.
If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
Enjoy the site, enjoy the submissions and enjoy your life. We will you the best as you teach English and travel the world. That's an amazing thing! Celebrate and investigate, collaborate and commiserate, laugh and cry, shake your head and wonder why. That's what TESall is all about.
Site Administrator will make the final decision on any and all information, posts, requests, etc. for posting on this site. Please read the Terms of Use and Privacy Policy regarding further information on the use of this site. If you have any questions, please feel free to contact us. You can learn more about Icon Education Group here.
Welcome to the wonderful world of TESOL!
Graduate your school to true tablet-driven education with Icon Educate Digital Learning Solution
Featured Postings:
Post
job
Today!
Post
resume
Today!
Post
teacher
Today!
Post
tutor
Today!
Post
course
Today!
Post
resource
Today!
Post
school
Today!
Post
classified
Today!
Post
recruiter
Today!
Post
lesson
Today!
Post
information
Today!
Post
scam
Today!
Things To Consider Before You Teach In The Middle East
Going to teach in the Middle East can be an amazing and rewarding experience. You'll get to experience new and exciting cultures, make friends with people you mig
Advantages of Getting a CELTA For Teaching English
When I first thought about teaching English in a foreign country many of my friends said to me I shouldn't bother getting a certificate to teach, most private students don't ask to see it, and getting a job in an academy restricts your ability to travel. Well I disregarded their advice and applied f
Working With Foreign Cultures
Cultures differ in how they communicate, how they use their time, and how they view themselves in terms of empowerment and decision making. The main variables we wi
Investigation of EFL Language Learners’ Strategies and Motivational Or
The aim of this study was to explore the relationship between English Language Learning Strategies (LLSs) and motivational orientations including Amotivation, Extrinsic orientation and Intrinsic orientation. To do so, 131 university students, studying English as a Foreign Language (EFL), by use of c
EFL/ESL Teaching Strategies for Low-Level Learners
Less-proficient readers read and process what they have read at a slower rate than most of their peers.
Teaching English to Children in Japan is Easy with the Right Tools
Kids have the attention span of an ant! Why wouldn't they? They have everything they could ever want given to them in a New York second.
Your biggest competition i
© Copyright - TESall - Icon Education Group
Home | About | FAQ | RSS | Advertise | TESOL Blog | Terms | Privacy | Contact
Top
Welcome to TESall.com. Ours is the first vertical search portal dedicated to the community of TESOL teachers teaching English abroad. You will find jobs and resources specifically for Teaching English to Speakers of Other Languages. Our ESL EFL TESOL jobs board contains the best jobs teaching abroad in countries around the world.
Job listings are gathered from around the web and the listings are updated daily. The jobs are categorized by region and include opportunities for teaching children in schools, private language schools and organizations offering classes for adults. These programs are designed for professionals and you can find listings by region to quickly locate jobs in your preferred countries.
In addition to jobs, TESall.com offers a wide variety of other resources for teaching abroad. Browse our website to find information about teachers, TESOL training, resumes, lesson plans, resources and more. we have articles about finding work, teaching in foreign countries and the requirements for teaching English abroad and a forum for discussions with other teachers.
Sign up today to gain access to all the resources we offer for Teaching English to Speakers of Other Languages. Post your resume or list your services as a tutor to find an employment opportunity for teaching abroad that fits your qualifications and preferences. Look for ideas for lessons or join in the discussion in our forums to connect with other professionals teaching English abroad and get advice and tips from your colleagues. You can find it all in one place at TESall.com.
